<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" xml:base="https://psfla.net/" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>PSFLA blog</title>
    <link>https://psfla.net/</link>
    <atom:link href="https://psfla.net/blog.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <description>blogposts for the website psfla.net!</description>
    <language>en</language>
    <item>
      <title>got linux working ^_^ - 5/19/25</title>
      <link>https://psfla.net/blog/linuxup/</link>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;hi&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;recently, i&#39;ve been getting into linux! coincidentally (and &lt;em&gt;actually&lt;/em&gt; coincidentally) windows 10 is reaching end-of-life&lt;br&gt;
i still have windows 10 installed, and i will use it for things like fl studio, but i just wanted to get into linux again for the hell of it! and i don&#39;t plan on upgrading windows any time soon :p&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;i&#39;m posting here as i finally got flash working, as well as other basic features! (like being able to update my sites...)
this means i will be able to update more again! :D&lt;br&gt;
additionally, i will be trying to update more consistently by coming up with commands if none are submitted within like. two days. people won&#39;t gee ay eff about this mspa if i don&#39;t update it!&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 18 Jun 2025 19:00:00 CDT</pubDate>
      <dc:creator>jade floase</dc:creator>
      <guid>https://psfla.net/blog/linuxup/</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>new navbar done! - 5/15/25</title>
      <link>https://psfla.net/blog/navbar/</link>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;hi!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;just finished the new navbar. it was kind of a pain to figure out how to make the background images pixelated...&lt;br&gt;
what they don&#39;t tell you in (w3)schools is that &lt;code&gt;image-rendering: pixelated;&lt;/code&gt; applies to background images too!!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;i&#39;m wondering if i should make a discord server but like. it feels a little early to be making one. so im probably gonna wait until i feel like PSFLA has an actual following&lt;br&gt;
in the meantime... sign the new &lt;a href=&quot;https://psfla.atabook.org/&quot;&gt;guestbook!&lt;/a&gt; i literally just made it :D&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;but um... yeah! gonna start working on updates more soon. i&#39;m really excited i feel like i actually have people looking at my MSPAs now :3&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://psfla.net/blog/&quot;&gt;back?&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 14 May 2025 19:00:00 CDT</pubDate>
      <dc:creator>jade floase</dc:creator>
      <guid>https://psfla.net/blog/navbar/</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>psfla.net is UP-TO-DATE!! - 5/10/25</title>
      <link>https://psfla.net/blog/domainlive/</link>
      <description>&lt;h2&gt;&lt;em&gt;finally, people will be able to view what i have been doing for the past week!!!&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;yeah. finally got the 11ty version of this site to the point where i feel like i can call it the &amp;quot;main version&amp;quot; of this site!&lt;br&gt;
you can find the php version &lt;a href=&quot;https://php.psfla.net/&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;here&lt;/a&gt;, but it won&#39;t be updated anymore.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;like most rewrites of sites i create, this rewrite was made because the backend of php PSFLA was a mess. now, the backend is less of a mess!&lt;br&gt;
it&#39;s still a mess though. you can check out the source &lt;a href=&quot;https://github.com/psfla/11tyserver&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;here&lt;/a&gt;, if you&#39;re so inclined&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;i&#39;m hopefully planning to update this site more, as well! fixing the quickprompt not displaying in firefox-based browsers should help with getting prompts, but i plan to write my
own prompts if nobody responds for long enough. more promo across the indieweb might also help with getting prompts, but that&#39;s just something i&#39;ll have to keep in mind :p&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h2&gt;- jade&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://psfla.net/blog/&quot;&gt;back?&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 09 May 2025 19:00:00 CDT</pubDate>
      <dc:creator>jade floase</dc:creator>
      <guid>https://psfla.net/blog/domainlive/</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>blog finished! - 5/8/25</title>
      <link>https://psfla.net/blog/blogfinished/</link>
      <description>
&lt;p&gt;hi! welcome to the first REAL blogpost on this site
&lt;br&gt;i&#39;m remaking PSFLA with 11ty! this is due to the previous php version being a mess to manage.
&lt;br&gt;this will also make it compatable with &lt;a href=&quot;https://nekoweb.org/&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;nekoweb&lt;/a&gt;&#39;s hosting options... i already use nekoweb for hosting my &lt;a href=&quot;https://thepersonever.net/&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;personal site&lt;/a&gt;, and my supporter tier includes hosting multiple sites!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;this site is not yet finished, however... i still have to finish the javascript portion of my mspa reader, so that it runs about as fast as mspfa&#39;s. until that point, the php version of PSFLA will still be present on the &lt;a href=&quot;https://psfla.net&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;psfla.net&lt;/a&gt; domain, and the 11ty version will be hosted on &lt;a href=&quot;https://psfla.nekoweb.org&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;psfla.nekoweb.org&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;small&gt;pst. if you&#39;re seeing this, that means you&#39;re looking at the 11ty version!&lt;/small&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2&gt;- jade&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;a href=&quot;https://psfla.net/blog/&quot;&gt;back?&lt;/a&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 07 May 2025 19:00:00 CDT</pubDate>
      <dc:creator>jade floase</dc:creator>
      <guid>https://psfla.net/blog/blogfinished/</guid>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>